{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530812816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530812815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" b9de302e-0833-4883-9af8-52dba216f18a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_V_Y-V-F"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530818050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530818049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" b9de302e-0833-4883-9af8-52dba216f18a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_V_Y-V-F"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530829389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530829389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530830426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530830425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530833099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530833099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530834133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530834133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530836932","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530836931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530837970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530837970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530840800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530840800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530841839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530841839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530844377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530844377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530845412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530845412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530847898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530847898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530848208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530848208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530849014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530849014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530851398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530851398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530856556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530856556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530857602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530857601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530880526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530880525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530881652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530881652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530884945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530884945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530885997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530885995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530889899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530889899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530890958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530890957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530913587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530913587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530914662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530914662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530927827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530927827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530928908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530928907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530940270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530940270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530941327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530941327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530946778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530946777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530947863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530947862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530987533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530987533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530988595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530988595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530992345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530992344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530993424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530993424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530998310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530998310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548530999370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548530999370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531002250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531002250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531003290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531003289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531011311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531011311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531012369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531012369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531015749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531015749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531016799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531016799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531023470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531023469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531024545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531024545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531042696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531042696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531043769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531043768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531068090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531068090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531069157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531069157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531072631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531072629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548531072738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548531072738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548532338530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548532338530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 01a606d2-5b63-4746-b170-c893c11dfb78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559100522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559100521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559105957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559105957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559109683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559109683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559112881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559112881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559117841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559117841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559122464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559122464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559126928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559126928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559130844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559130844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559134668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559134668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559138268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559138268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559144363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559144363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559161795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559161794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559166909","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559166909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559170108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559170108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559173763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559173763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559179401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559179401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559183200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559183200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559186657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559186656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559192491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559192491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559198393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559198392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559204157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559204157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559208820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559208820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559213046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559213046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559217420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559217420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559220544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559220543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559224768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559224768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559229116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559229116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559234896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559234895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559242701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559242701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 7565fc35-4265-42ca-adc1-fa71e08a9477"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559252267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559252266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559254398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559254398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559256546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559256545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559259771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559259770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559262046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559262046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559264284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559264283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559267167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559267167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559269378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559269378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559271570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559271569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559274864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559274863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559277012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559277010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559279101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559279101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559282070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559282070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559284282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559284282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559286535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559286534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559289712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559289710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559292073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559292073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559294443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559294442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559297502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559297502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559299672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559299672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559301849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559301849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559304959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559304959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559307124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559307124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559309323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559309323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559312512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559312512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559314944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559314943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559317372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559317372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559320533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559320532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559322773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559322773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559325059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559325059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559328104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559328103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559330332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559330332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559332573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559332573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559335548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559335548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559337900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559337900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559340294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559340294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559343452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559343452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559345836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559345836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559348254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559348254"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559351258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559351257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559353552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559353552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559355860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559355860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559359175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559359175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559361408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559361407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559363703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559363702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559367135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559367135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559369622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559369622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559372078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559372078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559374965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559374965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559377174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559377174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559379370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559379370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559382852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559382851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559385182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559385182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559387503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559387502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559390738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559390737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559393032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559393031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559395332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559395331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559398455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559398454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559400595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559400595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559402737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559402737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559405918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559405918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559408166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559408166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559410430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559410430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559413667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559413666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559415894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559415894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559418127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559418127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559421438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559421438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559423757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559423757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559426102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559426102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559429238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559429237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559431593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559431593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559433945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559433945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559437336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559437330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559437449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559437449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" 5aa4d3de-aa8a-4ce4-b0bf-f7d17085b627"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559448709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559448709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559448891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559448890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559449228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559449227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559450384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559450384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559451118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559451117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559454324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559454324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALASIRI"," userResponse":" ALASIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559454961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559454961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559455745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559455745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559456596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559456596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559457549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559457548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIOKOTA"," userResponse":" AKIOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559458249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559458249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559461176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559461175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUHUDIA"," userResponse":" ALISHUHUDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559461888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559461887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIO"," userResponse":" TUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559462907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559462907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LISILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559463093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559463092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559463866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559463866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559466956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559466956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559467778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559467777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISTARI"," userResponse":" MISTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559467844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559467844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559468444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559468444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559469057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559469057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559469845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559469845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559473238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559473238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGUSHA"," userResponse":" ALIANGUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559473867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559473866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559474547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559474547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559477500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559477500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559478401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559478400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559479485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559479485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559480658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559480658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" WANAKIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559484039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559484038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559484430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559484429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559485061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559485060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559486268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559486268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" WAMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559486938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559486937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559488408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559488407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559489256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559489256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559492246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559492246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559493230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559493230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559494115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559494114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559494768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559494768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKA"," userResponse":" SHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559495810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559495809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559497087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559497084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INANING"," userResponse":" INANING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559497095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559497095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" INIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559497968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559497968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559499066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559499065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559501467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559501466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559502230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559502230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559503096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559503096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559505169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559505169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559505713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559505712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559506480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559506480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMWAGA"," userResponse":" ANAMWAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559506983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559506983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559507767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559507767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559508431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559508431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559509275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559509275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559512230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559512229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559513034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559513033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559514622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559514622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUBALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIKUBALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559514854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559514854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559515397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559515396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559516192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559516192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559516827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559516827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559517890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559517890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWAMINI"," userResponse":" WAKIMWAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559518381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559518381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559520752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559520752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUNDI"," userResponse":" VIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559521169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559521169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559521732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559521731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIWILI"," userResponse":" VIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559523107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559523106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIBISHANA"," userResponse":" VILIBISHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559526514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559526513"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559527461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559527461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559528212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559528212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559528450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559528450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559529055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559529055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559529905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559529905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKEA"," userResponse":" ALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559530094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559530093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559530740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559530740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559532573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559532573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKOSEA"," userResponse":" MMEKOSEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559533350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559533350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOTE"," userResponse":" NYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559536405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559536405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559537229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559537229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559537878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559537878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559538481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559538481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559538870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559538870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559539069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559539069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559539806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559539806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559542739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559542736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559543400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559543400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559544256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559544255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559545027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559545027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559545810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559545810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559548338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559548337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559549530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559549530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMJAWAHI"," userResponse":" HUMJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559550325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559550324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559551106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559551106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559554101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559554100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559556464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559556464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559556485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559556485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559556521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559556521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559556533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559556532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559556547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559556547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559556561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559556561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559557432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559557431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559558304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559558304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559561227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559561226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIULIZA"," userResponse":" WALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559561718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559561718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559562464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559562464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559563553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559563552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559563960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559563960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559564670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559564669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559567804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559567803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559568768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559568767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559569541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559569534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559570202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559570202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559571126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559571126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559573750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559573749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559574556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559574556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559575389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559575386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559577963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559577963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559578578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559578578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559579170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559579169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559580156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559580155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559581063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559581063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559582122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559582121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEENDA"," userResponse":" AMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559582693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559582693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559585343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559585340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559585446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559585446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" e13b0c5f-c7a7-4fa6-9175-d44fd772427c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559597569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559597569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559604462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559604462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559606068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559606067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559609627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559609627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559611220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559611220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559614752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559614750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559616325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559616324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATOTO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559620243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559620243"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATOTO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559621862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559621862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559625999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559625999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559627588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559627587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKIRUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" WAKIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559631412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559631411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKIRUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559632972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559632972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WADUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559636766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559636766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WADUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559638327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559638327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559642572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559642572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559644134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559644133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559647544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559647544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559649108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559649108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559652773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559652773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559654796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559654796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548559654960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548559654960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190126_222637"," gameId":" c48b37f6-4efe-44ab-b996-05444f913812"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}